你被监视着
You are being watched.
政府有一套秘密系统
The government has a secret system--
一台每时每刻都在监控你的机器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
联系系统管理员
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror
身份不明
但它却看到了一切
but it sees everything--
身份不明
牵涉普通人的暴力罪行
violent crimes involving ordinary people.
政府认为这些人无关紧要
The government considered these people irrelevant.
关键执行人
我们不
We don't.
失踪
关键执行人
受当局追捕  我们只能秘密活动
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.
状态：纽约警局任职
你永远找不到我们
You'll never find us.
但无论是受害人还是行凶者
But victim or perpetrator,
只要你的号码被列出来  我们就会找到你
if your number's up, we'll find you.
疑犯追踪
第二季 第十七集
旧金山
威胁分析
异常活动
审检主体
丹佛
阿尔伯克基
圣路易斯
芝加哥
纽约
威胁分析
确定威胁
归类:
不相关
发布风暴警报  范围涉及沿海地区的
The storm warning is for the coastal areas
信号中断
运行诊断
拿桑郡和萨福尔克郡
of Nassau and Suffolk counties,
包括汉普顿东南部及欧文岛
including east and south Hampton and Owen Island.
曼哈顿
信号中断
外部故障
来源确认
温带风暴
风力: 九级
最大风速: 71公里/小时
豪雨和飓风
Heavy rains and destructive winds
无信号
将整夜持续
will continue into the night.
当地居民已被劝疏散
Residents are advised to prepare for evacuation.
维拉电影院
经典怀旧
《罗生门》
《雨族》
穿这种服务犬背心有点不道德吧
Isn't this service vest a little unethical?
我虽不愿自视残障  里瑟先生
I am handi-capable, Mr. Reese,
但我还是需要帮助的
but I need some assistance.
可不能把小熊排除在我们的雨天活动之外
We don't want to exclude Bear from our rainy day activities.
我们应该看《西部往事》[西部动作片]
We should have seen Once Upon A Time In The West.
字幕少啊
Fewer subtitles.
我们无限缅怀的已故肖特工有消息吗
Any word from our dearly departed Agent Shaw?
一点没有
Not a whisper.
我目前更忧心的是我们
What worries me more at the moment is that we haven't
最近也没有收到机器的消息
heard anything from the machine recently either.
是啊  我注意到了  三天没号码了
Yes, I've noticed. Three days. No numbers.
也许我们终于成功净化社会了
Maybe we're finally cleaning up the streets.
我倒是想
As much as I'd like that,
我不得不考虑这是否
I have to wonder if it hasn't got something to do
与真正已故的卡拉・斯坦顿有关
with the actually departed Kara Stanton.
你穿炸弹背心那会儿她上传的病毒
The virus that she uploaded during the time you spent in your bomb vest
可以轻易从国防部的系统中渗出
could easily have spread from the Department Of Defense systems,
感染到机器
all the way to the machine.
你造的机器  芬奇  你没访问权限吗
You built the machine, Finch. Can't you access it?
偷偷检查一下呗
You know, check under the hood?
我封闭它是有原因的  里瑟先生
I sealed it for a reason, Mr. Reese.
恐怕我们只能等着看
I'm afraid we're going to have to wait and see
斯坦顿的雇主有何打算了
what Stanton's employers have in mind for the future.
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：沙沙  somehacker  面条打包子  乖宝宝运气好  电风扇  板栗桑  天朝直属
特效：WiLL     时间轴：烟幕迟迟   擦擦   Jessie
翻译&校对&压制&总监：阿好
也许你的机器真出故障了
Maybe your machine really is on the fritz.
这之前发生过吗  芬奇
Has this ever happened before, Finch?
这是第一次
It's a precedent.
像这样一次给出六个号码
It gave us all six numbers at once?
还遍及全国吗
Spread out across the country like this.
令人忧心
Very worrisome.
还彼此陌生  我找不到他们之间的任何联系
Stranger yet, I can find no solid connection between them.
也许他们在一起搞什么阴谋
Maybe they're plotting something together.
或者有人在针对他们搞阴谋
Or someone's plotting against them.
我深表怀疑
I wondered that.
这六个号码中有三个出现在国家犯罪信息中心
Three of the six numbers are listed on the NCIC
失踪人口数据库
Missing Persons Database.
另外有两个在网上完全空白
Two of the others dropped off the grid entirely.
毫无网络数据资料
No digital footprint at all.
想隐藏什么  或者在躲藏什么
People with something to hide or hiding from something.
有个本地的  杰克・洛林斯
And there's one local. Jack Rollins.
他是布鲁克林的古董商
He's an antiques dealer in Brooklyn.
他还没报失踪
He hasn't been reported missing yet.
有可能就是下一个目标
That could be the next target.
我去打声招呼
I'll go say "Hi".
我去请卡特帮忙另外五个号码
I'll enlist Carter's help looking into the other five.
我会注意机器的异常行为
And I'll keep an eye on the machine's erratic behavior.
看来洛林斯是在家里开店的  芬奇
Looks like Rollins runs his shop out of his apartment, Finch.
没人应答  我就自行进入了
There's no answer, so I'm going to let myself in.
洛林斯对古董的品味挺独特
Rollins' taste in antiques is exotic.
没有他个人的踪迹
No sign of the man himself.
不过已经有人来过了  费了不少劲
But someone was already here and went to a lot of effort
在查一间欧文岛的物业租赁凭单
to dig up a bill for a rental property out on Owen Island.
我找到杰克・洛林斯的信用卡账单了
I found the account for Jack Rollins' visa.
支付了一笔海滨物业租金
Payments on the beach property
还有一张去萨福尔克郡的车票  都是24小时内付的
and a train ticket to Suffolk county, all in the last 24 hours.
洛林斯急于出城啊
Rollins was in a hurry to get out of the city.
我们不是唯一找他的人
And we're not the only ones looking for him.
在这种风暴天出门
Heading out in a storm like this?
洛林斯是在躲避什么
Rollins is running from something.
我去查查欧文岛怎么回事
I'll find out what's on Owen Island.
里瑟先生  这样好吗
Mr. Reese, is that a good idea?
风雨无阻  芬奇  既然洛林斯是我们唯一的线索
Storm or no, Finch, if Rollins is our one lead,
我就要去海滨
I'm headed to the beach.
下次要我帮忙时
Next time you need a favor,
等到雨季结束行不
can we wait till after the monsoon season?
感谢帮忙  莫斯
Thanks for your help, Moss.
-档案好像有点薄  -因为这些案子本来就薄
- These files seem a little thin. - Because the cases are thin.
人们消失的原因很多
Dozens of reasons people step off the grid.
信用问题  前科纪录
Bad credit, old rap sheet.
靠  有些人反正就失踪了  警探
I mean, hell, sometimes people just disappear, Detective.
第一个失踪的人是法国学生
First person to go missing was a French student
在斯坦福留学  七年之前了
studying abroad at Stanford, seven years ago.
毕业生流浪瘾大发  不足为奇
Post-collegiate wanderlust. Wouldn't be the first.
你发现什么特别的了
What's your interest?
档案底部的名字是谁
What's the name at the bottom of that file?
其他人的档案上也有
It's on the others too.
阿兰・费伊
Alan Fahey.
电脑中心的文职人员
Desk jockey at our CCSR branch.
处理网络犯罪  身份偷窃
Handles cybercrimes, identity theft,
大多是白领犯罪
mostly white collar stuff.
看来他整理了很多报告
Looks like he files one hell of a report.
是啊  有很多笔记
Yeah, he has a lot of notes.
看来他在查什么
Seems like he's on to something.
如果你有需要  我可以打电话给他
If you want, I can give him a call.
-问问他  -不用  可以了
- See what he's-- - No, that's okay.
我来跟进吧
I can handle the follow-up.
好吧  那我顶雨回家了
Well, I'm gonna beat the rain home.
好
Okay.
摩斯特工
Agent Moss?
我干这行很久了
I've been doing this job a long time.
或许太久了点
Probably too long.
卡尔・比彻的事
All that business about Cal Beecher...
你了解什么
What do you know?
我干我这行也很久了
Been doing my job for a long time too.
没有内务部档案的情况下  我只能猜测
And not having those IAB files, I can only surmise,
他们亮起那么多红灯
but the kind of red flags they put up,
比彻有大麻烦
Beecher is bad news.
避开吧  卡特
Steer clear, Carter.
我是费伊特工
This is Special Agent Fahey.
我是纽约警局的卡特警探
This is Detective Carter of the NYPD.
我在查一些失踪人员的档案
I've been looking through some missing person files
上面有你的笔记
that have your notes on them.
这些案子有一点共同之处
The cases were connected through one potential MO,
那些消失或损毁的照片
something about missing or destroyed photos
你在多处犯罪现场都发现了
you uncovered at more than one potential crime scene.
这一模式你有没有查到新线索
Have you been able to chase down any new leads on that MO?
我在华盛顿总部工作  警探
I work out of headquarters in DC, Detective.
我不追查线索  我只写报告
I don't chase leads. I write reports...
还没人看
that no one reads.
好吧  但我有个线人
Right. But I might have a new informant
有关于本案的新信息
with additional information for this case.
我是几个月前整理那些信息的
Well, I put all that information together months ago.
当时我打电话给纽约警局
I called the NYPD at the time.
没人帮得上忙
No one there was helpful.
没人有其他信息
No one had anything to add.
现在突然冒出新的消息了
Now something suddenly just popped up?
是保密消息来源
It's a confidential source.
对联调局保密  想得美
Confidential from the FBI? Nice try.
如果有新消息打给局里联络处
Call the bureau liaison if you have any new information,
不然就再见了
otherwise have a nice day.
恭喜你有新
Congratulations on your new...
欧文岛
他们在疏散这个岛  芬奇
They're evacuating the island, Finch.
但我还是到了洛林斯租下的房子
But I made it out to Rollins' rental house.
你在哪
Where are you?
我回到了布鲁克林  洛林斯的家里
Well, I'm back at Rollins' in Brooklyn.
在黑暗里摸索
Bumping around in the dark.
风暴毁了楼下的变压器
Storm knocked out a transformer down on the street
周围九个街区全部断电
and all power within a nine-block radius.
干嘛又回去
Why go back there?
卡特警探和一名联调局特工聊了聊
Detective Carter spoke with an FBI agent
他发现了那些案件有个模式
who's discovered a pattern in the crimes.
那些失踪人员的家里都没有照片
There were no photographs of the missing persons at their homes.
所以我在查看照片  到底有没有
So I'm looking for photos, or a lack thereof.
这是什么
What's this?
地下储藏室
"Basement storage."
得下楼看看了  小熊
I'm gonna take a look downstairs, Bear.
没什么可担心的
Nothing to worry about.
空相框  和其他人一样
Empty photo frames. Just like the others.
里瑟先生  我在洛林斯的地下室有发现
Mr. Reese, I've found something interesting in Rollins' basement.
芬奇  我听不见
Finch, I didn't copy.
芬奇
Finch?
这儿还有别人
I'm not alone.
小熊
Bear?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
什么东西
What is it?
里瑟先生  我想我弄明白了
Mr. Reese, I think I know what happened
那些失踪的人出了什么事
to all those missing people.
联调局  不许动
FBI, don't move.
举起手来  拿出身份证明
Hands up. I want to see some ID.
到底哪个
Well, which is it?
是要我举起手  还是要看身份证明
You want my hands up, or you want to see ID?
詹宁斯  美国法警
Jennings. US Marshals Service.
我在找一个人  名叫洛林斯
I'm trying to locate someone, a guy named Rollins.
有些问题要问他
Got some questions for him.
你在找洛林斯  我也是
You looking for Rollins? Me too.
我确信他和
I believe he's connected to--
和其他失踪案有关
To another missing persons case.
我们相信有一名通缉逃犯在找洛林斯
We believe a wanted fugitive may be looking for Rollins.
他在这儿吗
Is he here?
我不知道  才刚开始找
I don't know. I just started looking.
我们何不放下武器
Well, why don't we take our weapons off each other
搜查这栋房子
and clear this house?
洛林斯一案有新发现
Trail was hot on Rollins,
但总部没人能腾出手来  跟进线索
but no one at HQ would get off their hands, follow up the lead.
我就决定亲自看看
So I decided to come out here myself.
你一个人来的吗
You out here all alone?
虽然从匡提科毕业好多年了
Well, it's been a few years since Quantico,
但我还记得点儿外勤工作
but I remember a thing or two about working in the field.
这条线索你跟对了
Well, you're on the right trail.
洛林斯最近在这待过
Rollins was here recently,
顶着这种风暴他也走不远
he couldn't have gotten far in this storm.
我车就在外面
My car is outside.
不如去当地警局吧
Why don't we head to the local police station?
我们需要更多人手
We're gonna need a few more guys on this.
有人想销毁牙齿
Someone tried to destroy these teeth.
但温度不够没烧化牙釉
But the flame wasn't hot enough to burn enamel.
可能要花点时间  不过
It could take some time, but...
如果死者有牙医记录
if the vic's dentals are on file,
就能查到他的身份
we could get an ID.
不行  我们没时间等
No, we can't wait that long.
如果那些牙是杰克・洛林斯的
Assuming that the teeth belong to Jack Rollins,
牙取下之前他应该已经死了
he was likely dead when they were removed.
倒也但愿如此
One would hope so, anyway.
凶手肯定很清楚怎么处理尸体
Well, whoever did this knows how to get rid of a body.
他们不只要他的命
They didn't just want to kill Rollins,
还要他彻底消失
they wanted him to disappear.
我们调查的不是单纯的连环失踪
We may be looking at more than a string of missing persons.
我们调查的是连环谋杀
We may be looking at a string of murders.
六个受害人
Six victims.
如果凶手能假装受害者的身份
If our killer can assume these identities,
那他应该冒充了这些失踪者
then he would be a composite of all these missing persons
而且不止一次了
in more ways than one.
我们调查的是连环杀手
We're looking at a serial killer.
芬奇  你在干什么
Finch, what are you doing?
里瑟在岛上找的人凶残至极
Mr. Reese is out on an island looking for a man violent enough
不惜拔掉人的牙齿
to pull out another man's teeth.
我无法警告他  只能亲自过去
And now I can't warn him. I have to get there myself.
去岛上的路肯定都封死了
I'm pretty sure all the roads are closed now.
你怎么能过去呢
How do you think you're gonna get out there?
用飞行执照
Think I'll use my pilot's license.
飓风马上就到
I got a nor'easter touching down right now.
岛上还有357个居民
I've got a population of 357 souls,
需要我撤离这岛  否则就来不及了
I've got to get off this island before I can't anymore.
警长已经在内陆负责疏散了
Chief of police is running the evacuation on the mainland.
这被水淹掉的小镇上就我一个警察了
I'm the law left in the town with half its ass underwater.
这是联邦要案
This is a matter of federal importance.
-我们要找这个人  -不认识
- We're looking for this man. - Don't recognize him.
他要是在这租房的  估计已经疏散了
But if he was a renter, he's probably been evacuated.
警长  警长  请回答
Chief? Chief, come in.
不介意我们打几个电话吧
Mind if we at least make a few phone calls while we are here?
当然
Sure.
只要手机和座机还能通
If the cell and land lines weren't down,
电还没停
the power wasn't out,
应急无线电还没赶在今天不能用了
and the emergency radio didn't pick today to crap out on me.
-还要别的吗  -要  这儿咖啡如何
- Anything else? - Yeah. How's your coffee?
先生们  虽然你们有管辖权
Hey, gents, you may have jurisdiction and authority here,
但你们不会有我的协助
but one thing you don't have is my cooperation.
现在  天是老大
For now, mother nature takes priority.
法警  我们不能傻坐在这里
Look, Marshal, we can't afford to sit around here
副警长不帮忙也一样
with or without the deputy's help.
我们调查的不是单纯的一起失踪
I don't think we're on the trail of just a missing person here.
我认为洛林斯已经死了  而且还不止他一个
I think Rollins is dead, and he may not be the only one.
我们在查的是个冷血的连环杀手
I think we're on the trail of a cold-blooded killer.
你之前怎么不说
You didn't want to share this earlier?
我也不确定
Well, I didn't know all the facts.
严格说来  这只是我的猜想
Technically, it's still just a theory.
话说  你知道毁尸灭迹吗
Tell me, what do you know about making a body disappear?
这里成空城了
This place is a ghost town.
是啊  我们局都执行风暴巡逻去了
Yeah. Our uni's are out on storm patrol.
你为什么过来
What brings you down here?
为你
You.
我想过打电话  不过你不接  是吧
I would have called, but you're not answering those, are you?
我就想亲自看看
So I decided to drop by,
也许你能告诉我  我做错了什么
and maybe you could tell me what I did wrong.
卡尔  我正忙着呢  以后再说
Cal, I'm working on something. I'll talk when I can.
那我回头再来
I guess I'll check in later.
你是怎么困在这岛上的
So how'd you get stuck on the island?
消声器进水了  引擎发动不了
We got water in the muffler and the engine died,
于是就到这了  卡莉和我
so we came here-- Carly and I.
这是我的新娘  卡莉
That's my new bride Carly over there.
我们刚刚结婚  都是牙科保健员
We just got married. We're both dental hygienists.
-这点我说过吗  -是的
- Did I say that? - Yes.
你之前说不止洛林斯一个人是什么意思
What did you mean earlier when you said Rollins wasn't the only one?
我认为我们在查的是连环犯罪
I think we're on the trail of several crimes.
我在调查分布在多个州的多起谋杀案
I'm looking at multiple murders across multiple states.
凶手肯定是先占用了受害人的身份
The killer must have taken the identity of his victim
然后才转向下一个目标
before moving on.
我一路追查到斯坦福的那个学生
I followed the trail back to that student at Stanford,
再查下去
then I worked forward.
发现每个受害人都是先搬迁至其他城市
It turns out every victim of the killer moved cities
然后在18个月之内就消失了
within 18 months of vanishing.
洛林斯搬到了纽约
Rollins moved to New York.
我就去了纽约  发现了租赁凭单
So I went to New York, found the rental bill.
跟着他到了欧文岛
Followed him out here to Owen Island.
那个盗用洛林斯身份出行的人
Whoever was traveling as Rollins
可能还在这个岛上
could easily still be on this island.
艾瑞卡  桥被淹没了
Erica, we just lost the bridge.
什么时候的事  斯坦
When did this happen, Stan?
几分钟之前
A few minutes ago.
我锁了酒吧
I locked up the bar,
看到贝基刚搞定A&P[连锁超市]的告示牌
I saw Becky finishing the boards on the A&P.
我们冲向大桥
We high-tailed it down to the bridge,
正好看到它被淹
just in time to see it go under.
退潮之前绝对过不去
No crossing it until the tides go down.
-这家伙又是谁  -丹尼斯・坎宁安
- And who's this guy? - Dennis Cunningham.
选错日子视察酒店
I picked a bad day to check up on my hotel.
所以是你在建那酒店了
So you're the guy building that hotel?
在天气好的时候
On my drier days.
我们已经开工90天了
We're 90 days out on that property.
-如果全被冲走了  -还有别人
- If it washes away-- - - There's more.
我们在过来的路上看到了
On the way here, we saw someone.
在码头那里
Down by the docks.
看起来像是准备离开岛吗
Did it look like it was trying to get off the island?
像是在自己备船
Looked like he was prepping a boat for himself.
我们得过去一趟
We have to get down there.
这里有五名滞留居民
I've now got five stranded people
我才不离开
and no way off this rock,
这才是我该待的地方
this is where I need to be.
当然  副警长
Absolutely, deputy.
所以我们去替你带他回来
So we'll go and bring him back here for you.
什么怪人会冒着生命危险
Special kind of man ricks his life
在这种天气出海捕鱼
in this weather for a few crustaceans.
伙计们  我只是个渔民
Whoa, fellas, I'm just a fisherman.
这一网下来可值不少钱
There's a lot of money in this haul.
我不知道这也犯法
I didn't know I was breaking a law.
你的身份证呢
You have ID?
在水上可没人要看它
Don't get asked for it on the water.
-你叫什么名字  -伊森・马特森
- What's your name? - Ethan Mattson.
伊森  你现在是在岸上
Well, Ethan, you're on land now.
-你跟谁在一起  -没别人
- Who's with you? - No one.
我知道你在那儿
I know you're there.
我这儿有15发子弹
I've got 15 shots here.
想想清楚
Think it over.
不要开枪
No need for shooting!
我只是想要逃离这风暴
I was just looking to get away from this storm is all!
你住在岛上吗
You from the island?
不  我想找个船上的工作
No, I was looking for some work on the boats.
被风暴困在这里了
Got stuck out here by the storm,
以为可以坐船出去
thought I'd ride it out.
把他们俩都带回警局
Let's get them both back to the station.
我不管你是谁
I don't care who you are,
都不能危害居民
you can't endanger my citizens
在镇中心强行迫降塞斯纳飞机
by landing your Cessna in the middle of my town.
那其实是德哈维兰海狸水上飞机
That actually a de Havilland Beaver.
怎么回事
What's going on here?
这个业余风暴追逐者
This amateur storm chaser
哈罗德・格尔被捕了
Harold Gull is under arrest.
他把水上飞机降落在了镇广场
He landed his float plane in the town square.
我需要一片水来降落  那里刚好
I needed a stretch of water to land and there was, well,
全是水
water everywhere.
-这些又是什么  -我的气象设备
- And what's all this? - My meteorological equipment.
我是全国风暴追逐者
I've been a certified member of the National Storm Chasers
及观测者协会十年的注册会员
and Spotters Association for over ten years.
副警长  虽然他很鲁莽
Deputy, despite this man's recklessness,
但你能等到风暴之后再治他的罪吗
could you book him with endangering our lives after the storm?
我们有更重要的事要解决
We have bigger things to worry about.
好吧
Fine.
但风暴过去
But when the storm ends,
我要狠狠收拾他
I'm hitting him with everything I've got.
斯坦  天开始黑了
Hey, Stan, it's getting dark out there.
你能给后面的发电机
You think you could put some more diesel
加点柴油吗
in the gennie out back?
好的
Yeah.
全国风暴追逐者协会  哈罗德
The National Storm Chasers Association, Harold?
管用啊  不是吗
Well, it worked, didn't it?
我们之前错了  这并不是犯罪团伙
We were wrong. This isn't a group conspiracy.
那些号码  他们都死了
Those numbers, they're all dead.
我们追踪的是凶手
And we're tracking their killer.
我知道
I know.
我不幸看到了
I had the displeasure of seeing
真正杰克・洛林斯的残骸  只剩下臼齿
all that was left of the real Jack Rollins, molars and all.
变态的战利品
Some twisted mind's idea of a trophy.
要是机器给出这六个号码是想告诉我们
What if the machine sent us all six numbers to tell us
有人一直在假扮那些人
that someone had been all of those people?
要是那个聪明的杀人犯感兴趣的不止是
What if a smart killer was interested not only
夺走性命  还有他们的身份
in taking lives, but in taking identities.
就像变色龙
Like a chameleon.
假扮成受害者  过他们的生活
Changing into his victims, living their lives
直到他厌倦了  就去找下一个目标
until he gets bored and moves on to the next.
要想找出这种杀手  我们需要考虑
To identify such a killer, we would want to consider
他曾是谁  他可能长什么样
who he has been, and what he might look like.
好吧  要如何辨认出
Okay, so how do you spot someone
擅长扮演别人的人呢
who's that good at being anyone else?
打扰下  法警
Excuse me, Marshal.
那个联调局的家伙叫你去下后面
That FBI guy needs to see you out back.
快来看这个  斯坦利扑灭的火
You need to see this. Stanley put them out.
有人想用柴油把这堆烧掉
Someone used diesel to try to cook the pile.
几分钟前凶手还在这儿
The killer was here minutes ago.
他近在咫尺
He's close.
而且他抛弃了"洛林斯"的身份
And he's shed the "Rollins" identity.
那他可能是里边的任何人
Then he could be anyone in there.
如果凶手就在他们之中
If the killer is among these people,
那他现在会很不自在  这打破了他的模式
then he's out of his element-- he's broken his pattern.
假设顶替受害者的身份  就是他的固有模式
Assuming the identities of his victims, it's part of his ritual.
现在洛林斯的身份证已烧毁
And now that Rollins' ID is burned,
他被困住了
he's trapped.
他肯定假扮了别的身份
He must have taken on another identity.
而顶着那身份他无处可去
And he can't go anywhere with it.
他跟我们一样困在这里
He's as stuck as we are.
为何机器不给我们他真实的身份
Why didn't the machine give us his real identity?
为什么玩游戏
Why play games?
我估计是他很聪明
I assume he's smart,
他删除了他的原始数据
and he digitally erased his original persona.
我就删了
I did.
我们要想办法找到他
Well, we need to find a way to hunt him.
也许我们可以  里瑟先生
We might be able to, Mr. Reese.
你了解风暴追逐吗
Are you familiar with storm chasing?
你在看什么
What are you watching?
我不知道你仍然忙得没空跟我说话
Didn't know if you were still too busy to talk to me.
其实  我正好需要多双眼睛帮我看看
Actually, I could use another set of eyes on something.
你看看
Take a look.
这是六个月前芝加哥一栋大楼的安保摄像头
This is a building-owned security camera in Chicago six months ago.
这是我在查的一个失踪人口
A missing persons I'm working.
这人叫洛林斯
Guy named Rollins.
这是他正在离店
This is him leaving his shop,
这是他第二天回来的画面
and him coming back the next day.
然后他就搬去了纽约
He moved to New York soon after.
你注意到什么
What do you notice?
这是同一个人吗
That the same guy both times?
-怎么这么问  -挺像
- Why do you ask? - That's a close match.
但锁门的人是左撇子
But the guy locking up is left-handed,
开门的人用右手
and the guy unlocking is a righty.
而且他高一点
He's also a couple inches taller.
-正是  -你在查什么
- Exactly. - What are you looking at here?
-高明抢劫案吗  -比那糟多了
-Some kind of elaborate robbery? - Something much worse.
我确定一下
So let me get this straight.
你想让我约谈
You want me to conduct a series of interviews
在局里的每一个人  还要这个人帮忙
with everyone on the station and you want this guy to help?
他是唯一一个在桥被淹后登岛的
He's the only one who arrived on this island after the bridge went out.
我知道他样子有点怪
I know he appears a little strange,
但他的包里确实装着有趣的装备
but he does have some interesting equipment in those bags.
好吧  除非他有指纹扫描仪
Yeah, well, unless he has a fingerprint scanner
以及暴力犯罪数据库
and the VICAP database,
否则他有什么是我们需要的
what does he have that we need?
费伊特工  对吗
Agent...Fahey, is it?
你了解地震仪吗
Are you familiar with the instantel seismograph?
防弹衣
Body armor?
我觉得我们似乎不必如此重装
I don't think we'll be taking too much heavy fire with this group.
詹宁斯  我朝九晚五大部分时间
Look, Jennings, I spend most of my nine-to-five
都坐在办公桌前
tethered to a desk.
我审讯过一些贪污和盗窃身份的窃贼
I've questioned a few embezzlers and some identity thieves.
但这次我们是要跟杀人犯共处一室
We're about to walk into a room with a killer.
那我躲在你身后
And I'll be standing right behind you.
谢谢  爱米斯先生
Thank you, Mr. Amis.
我是联调局的  正在岛上调查一单失踪人口案
I'm with the FBI, looking for a missing person on the island here.
我要问你些常规问题
I'd like to ask you a standard series of questions,
非常感谢您的配合
and I'd appreciate your cooperation.
-好  问吧  -这是杰克・洛林斯
- Okay, so ask. - This is Jack Rollins.
我想知道
I'm trying to establish
这个岛上谁最近和他联系过
who had contact with him on the island recently.
我不认识他
I don't recognize him.
每年的这个时候都没太多游客
We don't get too many tourists this time of the year,
但有的话我会在店里碰见
but I would have seen him at the store.
今晚在局里的几位你认识谁  贝姬
Who do you recognize at the station tonight, Becky?
我认识斯坦利很久了
I've known Stanley most of my life.
-你不认识谁  -度蜜月的那对
- Who don't you recognize? - That honeymoon couple for one.
你们两个在哪里认识的
And where did you two meet?
奥尔巴尼
We met in Albany.
你早前为何没疏散
Why didn't you evacuate earlier?
我说过了
I told you,
那一渔网能值几万块呢
I've got a few thousand bucks crawling around in those traps
你们非逼我扔码头上了
you made me leave down on the docks.
所以你就无视紧急状态通知
So you disregarded a state of emergency?
我得保住我的收成
I had to preserve my catch.
你经常一个人放网吗
You often pull in traps all by yourself?
-进展如何  -还行
- How's it going? - Good.
看到这些小波动了吗
See all these tiny waves?
这叫微震
They're called microseisms,
这些小起伏是心跳
and all these little bumps are the heartbeat.
这根针像感应地壳变动一样的感应心跳
The needle picks it up like it would a tectonic shift,
这里感应很多
and it's picking up a lot.
-其他人呢  -都没问题
- And everyone else? - I'm getting clean readings.
里面的金属会放大信号
The metal in the table amplifies it.
每个人都很平静
Everyone is steady.
酒吧老板斯坦利稍差一点
Stanley the bar owner is a little below average,
不过我想他应该有别的问题
but I think there might be something wrong with him.
没事  我想他血液的酒精浓度
No, I just think his blood alcohol level
都能发动割草机了
could start a lawn mower.
-不过那个渔夫呢  -他在紧张
- But that fisherman in there? - He's nervous about something.
我认识伊森・马特森
I know Ethan Mattson.
他在欧文住了五年了
He's lived on Owen for five years.
虽然他有点小麻烦  但他精通船务
He gets into some trouble, but he's good on the boats.
你想知道我不认识谁吗
Do you wanna know who I don't recognize?
欧文岛上一半的人知道坎宁汉地产
Half of Owen knows Cunningham Properties,
但我从来没跟他面对面打过招呼
but I can't say I've ever said "Hi" to his face.
还有那个流浪汉
And that drifter?
谁会大冬天到岛上来
I mean, who comes to an island in winter
找季节工作
looking for seasonal work?
温特女士  请问您做斯坦福大学
Ms. Winter, how long have you been the dean
学生事务处主任多久了
of student affairs at Stanford?
十  不  十一年了
10--no, 11 years.
我想您帮忙
I'm wondering if you could shed light
一件前学生失踪案
on a former student who went missing.
昂利・缪塞  他毕业于
Henri Musset? He graduated--
2005年  我记得昂利  他是留学生
In 2005. I remember Henri. He was an international student.
毕业后立刻就失踪了
He went missing right after he graduated.
警方寻找了数周
Police called for weeks.
法国派出了特派员  国际刑警都参与了
Inspectors from France, even Interpol.
那孩子在圣地亚哥有一条网络踪迹
There was a digital trail on the boy in San Diego,
在他毕业18个月后
18 months after graduating.
我们和警方也是这么说的
Just as we told the authorities then,
昂利从没留下过转寄地址
Henri never left a forwarding address.
我们经常会和毕业校友暂时失去联系
We often lose touch with recent alumni
直到他们安顿下来
until they settle down somewhere.
这么说最后一次见到昂利还是在校园里
So the last time Henri was seen was on campus.
他住学生公寓  当时有室友吗
He lived in student housing. Did he have a roommate?
有  最后一年的室友是名学生  叫亚历克斯・德克兰
Yes. His last year, it was a student named Alex Declan.
这上面说
It says here--huh.
怎么了
What?
我刚在昂利的住宿表格里看到条记录
I just see a note on Henri's housing form.
他在最后一个学期要求调换室友
He requested a new roommate his last semester.
最后一年的最后一个学期
The last semester of his senior year?
-这种事情常见吗  -不太常见
- Does that happen often? - Not usually.
大多数毕业生满脑子是其他很多事情
Most seniors have a million other things on their mind.
不过问题貌似解决了
But the matter seems to have been resolved.
你有德克兰的记录吗
Do you have any records on Declan?
奇怪
That's strange.
德克兰在住宿记录里是昂利的室友
Declan is listed in housing as Henri's roommate,
但我找不到他的入学登记
but I can't find his registration.
照片也没有
No student photo either.
肯定是什么地方弄错了
Something must have fallen through the cracks.
丹尼斯  你真是个大忙人
Dennis, you're such a busy guy.
都不怎么来岛上
You don't get out to the island very often.
我用不着天天守着地产
I don't babysit my properties.
不过酒店的进度晚了几天
But the hotel out here was days behind schedule.
你觉得我愿意大雨天逛沙坑吗
You think I want to slog around this sandpit in the rain?
维克托  你没有身份证明
Victor, you don't have an ID.
你没有任何来岛上的正当理由
You don't have a solid alibi for being here on the island
也没有去码头的正当理由
and, last of all, for being down at the boatyard.
我说过了  我只是路过而已
I told you. I was passing through.
认得这个吗  是你的东西
Recognize this? It's yours.
有很多的D型环
You've got a lot of D-rings.
有点奇怪
Kind of weird.
你要么是个登山者  要么
Unless you're a climber, or...
当过军人
in the military.
你心脏有问题吗
Do you have a heart problem?
因为现在  你的心脏在狂跳
Because right now, yours is really pumping.
欧文岛警局  我是乔丝・卡特警探
Owen Island station, this is Detective Joss Carter.
纽约市第八警局
Eighth Precinct, New York City,
在警用紧急频道呼叫
calling on the emergency police frequency.
能听到吗  完毕
Do you read me? Over.
我是欧文岛警局的施密特副警长
This is Deputy Schmidt of the Owen Island PD.
你是谁
Who is this?
卡特警探
Detective Carter
来自纽约市警局
from New York City.
我有消息
I have new information
要给在你岛上的法警
for the US Marshal on your island.
我需要立刻和他通话
I need to speak to him immediately.
谁
Who is it?
有个市里的警探呼叫
Some detective from the city got through,
说她叫什么卡朋特  卡特
said her name was Carpenter--Carter--
发电机
The generator.
能听到吗  完毕
Do you read me? Over.
上帝啊  她  她死了吗
Oh, my God. Is she--is she dead?
你不应该出去  风暴很强
You shouldn't go out there. The storm's pretty bad.
我在跟踪一条线索  很急
I'm following up on a lead, it's urgent.
我得去欧文岛
I need to get to Owen Island.
我不能让你去
I can't let you do that.
我不管有什么线索
I don't care what lead it is.
我要去  卡尔
I'm going, Kyle.
我不会说第二遍的
I won't say it again.
好  那我开车
Okay... but I'm driving.
什么情况
What's going on here?
先是审问我们  现在又这样
First you question us, and now this?
你  你也在帮他们
You. You were helping them.
他们到底在干什么
What were they doing in there, really?
他们征用了我的设备
They asked to use my equipment for police business.
从我们之中找说谎的人
They were looking for liars in the group.
说是要找到一个杀人犯
Talking about finding a killer.
贝基  他们问了你什么
Becky, what did they ask you?
他们问我认识这里的谁
They asked me who I recognized here.
那你不认识谁啊
Then who don't you recognized.
大家请冷静
Everyone please settle down.
你正在岛的另一端建酒店
You're building a hotel on the other side of the island.
却没人认识你
Nobody even knows your face.
我在市里有几百个商业伙伴
I have hundreds of business contacts in the city.
随便打个电话
Call any of them.
那么做有什么好处  哈罗德
And what good did that do, Harold?
行为分析  约翰  给点时间
Behavior analysis, John. Just give it a minute.
你呢  新郎先生  谁都不认识你
What about you, Mr. Newlywed? Nobody knows your face.
等等  我认识她
Wait a second, I know his face.
各位  咱们都忘了  她是被刀杀死的
Everybody, we're forgetting, she was killed with a knife.
-是谁的刀  -我知道是谁的
- So whose knife was it? - I know whose it is.
那是一把卡巴刀[兰博刀]
That knife? It's called a Ka-Bar.
在普通装具店是买不到的
Not exactly something you pick up at a local bait and tackle.
我没伤人
I didn't hurt anybody.
一般人不会
You need to be a special kind of person
携带那种武器
to carry a weapon like that.
放开我
Let me go.
如我所料
That's what I thought.
我是说谎了
I was lying.
行了吧
Okay?
上帝作证  我是说谎了  但我不是杀人犯
God help me, I was lying. But I'm not a killer.
没错  你是海军陆战队的
No. You're a marine.
那把刀  这纹身
The knife. The tattoo.
还有你包上挂的D型环
The D-rings clipped to your bag.
你是逃兵
You're on the run.
基地勒强营24期的
24th meu out of Camp Lejeune.
第二期兵役了
Second tour.
我不能回去
I couldn't go back.
我本想找船去加拿大
I wanted to get a boat to Canada.
结果被困在这儿了
I got stuck here.
谁还知道你有那把刀
So who else knew you had that knife?
我不知道
I don't know.
我是跟那个渔夫一起过来的
I mean, I came into the station with the fisherman.
等等  那个渔夫去哪儿了
Wait, where is the fisherman?
-他肯定是溜掉了  -我去追
- He must have slipped out. - I'll go after him.
如果我没回来  带这些人去安全地带
If I don't come back, get these people to safety.
你觉得我们跨州之前
So...do you think we can cross the entire state
你能说句话吗
before you say a word to me?
你想说什么
What do you want to talk about?
我能想到个话题
I can think of some things.
比如说一名纽约警探无法进入联调局
Like how an NYPD detective got aced out of the FBI
就因为择友不当  这话题怎么样
because she keeps bad company, how about that?
你在说什么  联调局
What are you talking about, the FBI?
跟内务部不太友好吧  卡尔
Not a friend of internal affairs, huh, Cal?
乔丝  我在缉毒队
Joss, I'm in narcotics.
每年我们都会被内务部查好几次
We get pulled in by IAB half-a-dozen times a year.
对我们来说不算什么
My neck of the woods don't mean a thing.
对我算
It does to me.
让我怀疑我是不是信任错了人
Makes me wonder about the man I trusted.
怎么  你不相信我吗
Oh, what, you don't trust me?
你觉得我腐败了  我受贿了吗
You think I'm dirty? That I'm on the take?
你是不是这么想的
Is that what you think?
我不知道该怎么想  卡尔
I don't know what to think, Cal.
他们到底跟你说了我什么
Yo, what did they tell you about me?
比彻  慢点
Beecher! Slow down!
真的吗
You serious?
怎么  你以为我会伤害你
What, you think I'd hurt you?
我不知道
I don't know.
可我不想伤害你
But I don't want to hurt you.
大麻
Marijuana.
这就是你想从风暴中拯救的东西
This is what you were trying to protect from the storm.
不  这不可能
Oh, no, that couldn't be.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
我们要找杀人犯
We're hunting a killer,
结果却跟这么个业余毒贩杠上了
and instead we get amateur drug night in the sticks.
你用你的船偷运这些东西吗
You smuggle it in on your boat?
别回答了  我要说对了你流点血就行
Ah, don't say anything. Just bleed if I'm right.
一般说来  我会把你送进监狱
Ordinarily, I'd make sure you went behind bars.
但我眼下另有要事
But I got bigger fish to fry.
先把你送进后备箱吧
So you go in the trunk.
联调局
FBI.
我哪里暴露了
What gave me away?
你怎么知道的
How did you know?
约谈间隔时的感应针孔
The needle spiked in between the interviews.
当时我没注意看
When I wasn't watching.
当时你在桌边休息
When you were resting on the table.
你应该注意下心率的
You should keep an eye on that heart rate.
我就知道你的水平远不止那种审问
I knew you were too good at those interrogations.
你到底是谁
Who are you really?
我也想问你一样的问题
I could ask you the same thing.
你比我预想的还要高一点
You're taller than I would have thought.
还剪了头发
And you cut your hair.
你完全相信了敬业的"费伊特工"
And you bought every minute of the dedicated "Agent Fahey".
是啊  演得挺好
Yes, quite the performance.
敢出声  我就开杀戒了
Make a sound, I start hurting innocents.
我们走走吧
Let's take a walk.
我想私密点的空间对我们俩都好
I thought a bit more privacy would do us some good.
事已至此
You know, the walls are closing in.
你无处可逃
You have no place to run.
结束了
It's over.
对费伊来说结束了  当然
It's over for Fahey, sure.
就像洛林斯来说结束了
Just like it was over for rollins.
你是在他们死前还是死后拔了牙
Was that before or after you tore teeth out of his head
扔进火炉的
and threw them in a furnace?
那倒霉东西烧不尽  有漏洞  我知道
Damn things never burn. Sloppy, I know.
但是联调局来敲门了
But when the FBI's knocking on your door,
动作要快一点才行
you have to move faster than you should.
会有其他特工来调查的
Other agents will come looking.
就像上一个那样吗
Like the last one?
联调局特工总是两人一起行动
Federal agents always work in pairs.
但是那个穿着愚蠢蓝色风衣的家伙单干了
But this hard-ass showed up solo in a stupid blue windbreaker,
敲我的门  问洛林斯的下落
knocking on my door, looking for Rollins.
他跟我说话
He talked to me.
看起来很紧张
Seemed nervous.
有点不太自在
A little out of his element.
然后我把他敲晕了
Right then I knew I had him beat.
我别无选择  只好杀了他
He left me no choice. I had to kill him.
然后我意识到离开这个岛唯一的办法
Then I realized my only way off this island
就是变成他
was to become him.
结果又遇到这场该死的风暴
Then this damn storm hits,
还有个法警牛仔来敲门
and some cowboy US Marshal comes knocking.
我只能继续扮演费伊特工
I was stuck as Special Agent Fahey,
就即兴发挥了
so I improvised.
还有那个副警长  为什么要伤害她
And the deputy. Why harm her?
我不确定她都从无线电里听到什么
Well, I couldn't be sure what she heard off the radio.
得时刻做好即兴发挥的准备啊
You always have to be ready to improvise.
说实话  问题不在于我是谁
Honestly, the question isn't who I am.
而是你是谁
It's who you are.
我观察了你一整晚
I watched you all night.
你看  我总能认出伪装者
See, I can always spot an impostor.
我认出了你
I spotted you.
你和我一样吗
Are you like me?
你根本不了解
You have no idea.
你不过是业余的
You're an amateur at this.
我可没打算这样
Not the way I planned it, man.
我不伤害人
I don't hurt people.
后备箱里的联调局探员也不是我杀的
And I didn't kill the FBI guy in that trunk.
但是你碍着事了  所以你得沉到海里
But you're in the way, so you go in the drink.
别担心
Don't worry.
水这么凉  很快的
As cold as this water is, it'll be quick.
伊森
Hey, Ethan.
有这么快吗
As quick as that?
费伊是扮不长了  我认为神秘的格尔先生
Now that Fahey won't get far, I think the mysterious Mr. Gull
可以成为下一个挑战
might be my next great challenge.
你永远无法离开这个岛
You'll never get off the island.
明早他们会赶来寻找真正的阿兰・费伊
By morning they'll come here looking for the real Alan Fahey.
他们会找到他
And they'll find him...
在他的后备箱里
in the trunk of his car.
那你呢
And what about you?
那  你呢
And what about...you?
你问的问题  就是答案
You asked the question and you're the answer.
你的飞机
Your plane.
你要带我飞离这里
You're gonna fly me out of here.
你的命还有用
You haven't outlived your usefulness.
你成不了我  因为我拯救生命
You could never be me because I save lives.
而你夺取生命
You take them.
不  我比那些人活得都要优质
No, I live those lives better than real people ever could.
我跟着他们  看他们挥霍自己拥有的一切
I follow them and watch them waste what they have.
我给予他们的身份以公平
I do those identities justice.
见我所见
The things I've seen.
活我所活
The lives I've lived.
等我找到我想成为的那个人  我会停手
One day I'll stop, when I find the person I'm meant to be.
什么
What?
像你这样的人无法停手
People like you don't stop.
你想怎么找借口都随你
You can rationalize it however you like.
但你伤害他人只因为你喜欢
But you hurt people because you like it.
只因为你变态
Because you're sick!
你心理失衡  你需要治疗
You're maladjusted and you need help.
再想想
On second thought,
我觉得还是换个方式离开这个岛
maybe I'll find another way off this island.
真遗憾不能进一步了解你
I'll miss finding out more about you.
还有什么没说的
If there's anything left to tell,
我继续生活时随便编下吧
I'll make it up as I go along.
别担心  我很擅长
Don't worry, I'm good at that.
就像你一样
Just like you.
-你没事吧  哈罗德  -警探
- You all right, Harold? - Detective?
你真是太及时了
You have impeccable timing.
你怎么过来的
How did you get here?
跟着海岸警卫队来了
I hitched a ride with the Coast Guard.
屋里面一些情绪激动的人说
And some very unpleasant people inside said they thought
他们看见你朝这边来了
they saw you come this way.
就是他吗  那位身份杀手
So is that him, our identity killer?
他扮成了联调局特工
He was pretending to be an FBI agent.
他是真的很擅长
He was really rather good at it.
他有警徽  配枪  还有
He had a badge and a gun and a--
还有什么
And what?
防弹衣
Body armor.
欧文岛
你在干什么
What are you doing?
这里是警局
It's a police station.
肯定会有这玩意儿
There's bound to be one of these around here somewhere.
听着
Hey, listen...
我不知道昨晚我们算怎么回事
I don't know what happened last night between us,
但是  我想知道今天怎么回事
but, uh, I'm wondering what happens today.
我不知道怎么回事
I don't know what happens.
但是我很高兴有你在
But I'm glad you were here.
昨晚有毒贩用捕鱼枪射我
A drug smuggler shot at me with a spear gun last night.
你是第一次遇到吗
Is that a first for you?
真希望是第一次
Wish I could say yes.
很高兴你回来了  里瑟先生
Glad you made it back, Mr. Reese.
我也是
I am too.
很高兴机器是对的
And I'm glad the machine was right.
怎么说
How so?
它很聪明  告诉我们凶手
It was smart enough to tell us about a killer
有着多重身份
with multiple identities.
也许出现六个号码不是故障
It may be true that the six numbers were not a glitch,
但之前三天的沉默是
but the three days of silence preceding it were.
如果机器正常运行
If the machine had been working properly,
我们也许就能拿到阿兰・费伊的号码
we might have gotten a number for the real Alan Fahey
然后救下他
and saved him.
而现在  却牺牲了一名联调局特工
Instead, an FBI agent is dead.
真希望知道这对未来意味着什么
But I wish I knew what that means for the future.
至少风暴过去了
At least the storm is passing.
不  里瑟先生  我感觉刚刚开始
No, Mr. Reese, I have a feeling that it's just beginning.